List<Map<String, dynamic>> PsycoPartOneQuestions = [
  {
    'question':
        'Which neurotransmitter is primarily associated with mood regulation and is often targeted in the treatment of depression?',
    'answers': [
      'Serotonin.',
      'Dopamine.',
      'Norepinephrine.',
      'Acetylcholine.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'A patient with schizophrenia who experiences false sensory perceptions, such as hearing voices, is most likely experiencing:',
    'answers': [
      'Obsessions.',
      'Delusions.',
      'Hallucinations.',
      'Paranoia.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the primary nursing intervention for a patient experiencing acute anxiety?',
    'answers': [
      'Administer antipsychotic medication.',
      'Encourage deep breathing exercises.',
      'Offer praise and compliments.',
      'Provide reality orientation.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following is a potential side effect of lithium, a mood stabilizer used in bipolar disorder treatment?',
    'answers': [
      'Hypertension.',
      'Weight gain.',
      'Respiratory depression.',
      'Tachycardia.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'In the context of therapeutic communication, what is the term for the nurse\'s ability to understand the patient\'s feelings and convey this understanding?',
    'answers': ['Empathy.', 'Sympathy.', 'Parroting.', 'Interjection.',],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'When assessing a patient for signs of alcohol withdrawal, which symptom is considered a medical emergency?',
    'answers': [
      'Nausea and vomiting.',
      'Tremors.',
      'Delirium tremens (DTs).',
      'Restlessness.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which defense mechanism involves attributing one\'s undesirable traits or actions to another person?',
    'answers': [
      'Projection.',
      'Displacement.',
      'Reaction formation.',
      'Rationalization.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which nursing intervention is a priority when caring for a patient with borderline personality disorder during a crisis?',
    'answers': [
      'Setting strict boundaries',
      'Offering reassurance and support',
      'Confronting manipulative behavior',
      'Administering antipsychotic medication',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which eating disorder is characterized by recurrent episodes of binge eating followed by inappropriate compensatory behaviors, such as vomiting or excessive exercise?',
    'answers': [
      'Anorexia nervosa.',
      'Bulimia nervosa.',
      'Orthorexia nervosa.',
      'Avoidant/restrictive food intake disorder.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which antipsychotic medication is known for its potential to cause agranulocytosis and requires regular blood monitoring?',
    'answers': ['Risperidone.', 'Olanzapine.', 'Clozapine.', 'Haloperidol.',],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which term describes a defense mechanism where a person refuses to acknowledge the existence of a threatening situation or problem?',
    'answers': ['Suppression.', 'Denial.', 'Regression.', 'Sublimation.',],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'A patient diagnosed with antisocial personality disorder is likely to exhibit which of the following characteristics?',
    'answers': [
      'Fear of abandonment.',
      'Impulsive and irresponsible behavior.',
      'Preoccupation with physical appearance.',
      'Extreme mood swings.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the primary goal of cognitive-behavioral therapy (CBT) in the treatment of depression?',
    'answers': [
      'Identifying unconscious conflicts.',
      'Increasing self-awareness.',
      'Changing negative thought patterns.',
      'Promoting relaxation.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'In the context of the Mental Status Examination (MSE), which component assesses a patient\'s ability to think abstractly and solve problems?',
    'answers': [
      'Memory.',
      'Orientation.',
      'Judgment and insight.',
      'Cognitive functioning.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following medications is commonly used to manage symptoms of attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder (ADHD)?',
    'answers': ['Lorazepam.', 'Methylphenidate.', 'Clozapine.', 'Lithium.',],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'When conducting a risk assessment for suicide, which factor is considered a strong predictor of suicidal intent?',
    'answers': [
      'Male gender.',
      'Social support.',
      'Previous suicide attempts.',
      'Religious beliefs.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which neurotransmitter plays a crucial role in the pathophysiology of Alzheimer\'s disease?',
    'answers': [
      'Serotonin.',
      'GABA (Gamma-Aminobutyric Acid).',
      'Acetylcholine.',
      'Dopamine.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which therapeutic approach focuses on helping patients identify and change irrational beliefs and thought patterns?',
    'answers': [
      'Psychodynamic therapy.',
      'Gestalt therapy.',
      'Rational Emotive Behavior Therapy (REBT).',
      'Dialectical Behavior Therapy (DBT).',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the primary purpose of administering antipsychotic medications to patients with schizophrenia?',
    'answers': [
      'To enhance cognitive functioning.',
      'To alleviate negative symptoms.',
      'To reduce positive symptoms.',
      'To prevent relapse.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'A patient diagnosed with generalized anxiety disorder (GAD) often experiences excessive worry and apprehension. Which class of medications is commonly used to treat GAD?',
    'answers': [
      'Benzodiazepines.',
      'Selective serotonin reuptake inhibitors (SSRIs).',
      'Antipsychotics.',
      'Mood stabilizers.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which nursing intervention is essential when caring for a patient with anorexia nervosa who refuses to eat?',
    'answers': [
      'Force-feeding the patient to meet nutritional needs.',
      'Allowing the patient to skip meals decreases anxiety.',
      'Providing emotional support and encouragement.',
      'Administering antianxiety medications.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'A patient with major depressive disorder is prescribed an antidepressant. Which medication should the nurse monitor closely for the risk of serotonin syndrome when combined with the antidepressant?',
    'answers': [
      'Acetaminophen.',
      'Aspirin.',
      'St. John\'s Wort.',
      'Vitamin C.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which theory of personality development emphasizes the role of unconscious conflicts and defense mechanisms?',
    'answers': [
      'Humanistic theory.',
      'Cognitive theory.',
      'Psychodynamic theory.',
      'Behavioral theory.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which symptom is commonly associated with borderline personality disorder (BPD)?',
    'answers': [
      'Delusions of grandeur.',
      'Splitting.',
      'Catatonia.',
      'Apathy.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'When providing care to a patient with post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD), which approach should the nurse prioritize?',
    'answers': [
      'Encouraging avoidance of traumatic memories.',
      'Promoting exposure therapy.',
      'Using confrontation to challenge beliefs.',
      'Offering a safe and supportive environment.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which therapeutic communication technique involves repeating the patient\'s words to encourage further discussion?',
    'answers': ['Clarification.', 'Paraphrasing.', 'Reflection.', 'Restating.',],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which phase of the nursing process involves identifying patient needs and developing a plan of care?',
    'answers': ['Assessment.', 'Planning.', 'Implementation.', 'Evaluation.',],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'In the context of substance use disorders, what is the term for a physiological reaction to the cessation of a substance to which the body has become dependent?',
    'answers': ['Tolerance.', 'Craving.', 'Withdrawal.', 'Intoxication.',],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which medication is commonly used to treat symptoms of mania in bipolar disorder?',
    'answers': ['Diazepam.', 'Lamotrigine.', 'Quetiapine.', 'Buspirone.',],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the primary goal of crisis intervention in psychiatric nursing?',
    'answers': [
      'To prevent the occurrence of crises.',
      'To provide long-term therapy.',
      'To stabilize the patient\'s condition.',
      'To address underlying childhood traumas.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'A patient with schizophrenia exhibits a flat affect, poverty of speech, and social withdrawal. These symptoms are classified as:',
    'answers': [
      'Positive symptoms.',
      'Negative symptoms.',
      'Cognitive symptoms.',
      'Affective symptoms.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which nursing intervention is essential when working with a patient diagnosed with dissociative identity disorder (DID)?',
    'answers': [
      'Encouraging the patient to suppress alter personalities.',
      'Promoting exploration of traumatic memories.',
      'Avoiding discussions about the disorder.',
      'Documenting each alter\'s behavior separately.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which personality disorder is characterized by a pervasive pattern of distrust and suspiciousness of others\' motives?',
    'answers': [
      'Antisocial personality disorder.',
      'Narcissistic personality disorder.',
      'Paranoid personality disorder.',
      'Histrionic personality disorder.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which nursing intervention is essential when caring for a patient with delirium?',
    'answers': [
      'Providing a calm and quiet environment.',
      'Administering antipsychotic medication.',
      'Encouraging physical restraints.',
      'Promoting isolation from family and friends.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'A patient experiencing alcohol withdrawal presents with hallucinations, severe agitation, and autonomic hyperactivity. Which condition should the nurse suspect?',
    'answers': [
      'Delirium tremens (DTs).',
      'Alcohol intoxication.',
      'Opioid overdose.',
      'Panic disorder.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which model of psychiatric care delivery emphasizes the importance of community-based services and minimizing hospitalization?',
    'answers': [
      'Medical model.',
      'Recovery model.',
      'Psychoanalytic model.',
      'Behavioral model.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which neurotransmitter is often implicated in the pathophysiology of obsessive-compulsive disorder (OCD)?',
    'answers': [
      'Serotonin.',
      'Dopamine.',
      'Norepinephrine.',
      'GABA (Gamma-Aminobutyric Acid).',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which ethical principle guides the nurse to respect a patient\'s right to make autonomous decisions about their treatment, even if the nurse disagrees with those decisions?',
    'answers': ['Beneficence.', 'Justice.', 'Autonomy.', 'Non-maleficence.',],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'When assessing a patient for symptoms of mania, which behavior is characteristic of this mood disorder?',
    'answers': [
      'Decreased energy and motivation.',
      'Pessimistic thoughts and feelings.',
      'Rapid speech and impulsivity.',
      'Apathy and social withdrawal.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'In the context of psychiatric nursing, what does the acronym "ECT" stand for?',
    'answers': [
      'Electrocardiogram Therapy.',
      'Electroconvulsive Therapy.',
      'Emotional Counseling Treatment.',
      'Excessive Cognitive Testing.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  }
];
